Hello Hello Hello Metro Channel Rating
Friends, in today's first video we have Weekly
Market, let's discuss all the
important news and indicators, see
such a cross in the indicators and updates with the video,
right now the market is again in a
good level of correction along with
consolidation, a reinforcement is going on,
some indicators of soil,
important technical support,
approaching Lewis, from Yoni Fit, now I have some long
term trend, by making conscious purchases, the
bar is retracing from there, so this quality can remain
for a few days, hence
we feel that this is a short time or picture of
Khatron chutney and try a little to keep
withdrawing your investment whenever you get a chance, keeping all these
news and indicators in mind,
which fundamental issues can you
collect for Kumaon University,
which can still give you a good valuation,
well and at which price level you can buy,
we will discuss that in this video
friends, if you have subscribed to our channel  If you have
n't subscribed yet, do it now and
press the "Subscribe" button because I keep
updating my list of best for all on a weekly basis and keep sharing it with you,
which should not be of much use to you
or limited, so
without taking any of your time, let's get
started friends, again the same thing,
in this video we are covering so many staff, so many
good staff are
available at good valuations, they are
available at pimples valuations, so we have to cover all those staff,
so I will
give a brief description of all the staff, I will not do a very
detailed discussion
on the business of their staff, we will only discuss
what all those companies do and
focus more on
what prices they have, there you
can start their item list,
but friends, the
first company of our discussion today is this small finance
bank, this small finance bank, but if we
talk about the best small
finance bank in India, then I will soon
make a positive computer on this,
those who do it should reduce making chapter wise positive
that  In which chapter, which stock
is best performing, best fundamentals
for best option for long term
investment, we will compare the small finance banks, there are
232 listed small
finance banks, compare them and
see that now we will see in this, this
used
Chanakya numbers look very good and stylish,
we have a very solid company with very solid numbers, it
operates in Rajasthan, it operates
in semi urban to rural areas, finance
friends remember it, so
this small finance market volume is the
best small finance in India, in today's first
video we discussed the results of
this small finance bank in off market flat,
their net
profit is good, base net
interest income is good, there is a
personal problem due to which
investors went to Facebook and some
effort was made, due to which you saw that there was a
decline of almost 1011 percent on Friday in this small finance bank,
you can see here, this is the last
candle, this is the glass Delhi channel, there was a decline of
1011 percent on it  There was a decline. This is a small
finance bank, but fundamentally it is a very
good company, it is a very balanced company.
Welcome & Company's financial ratios are
quite good. The only thing is that the net NPAs have
increased slightly to 2.2%,
but I think that is a short-term
problem. Now, as you can see,
Kuber's secondary sector has a greater impact on semi-urban and rural
areas,
hence it increases in the middle because this
company operates in Riyadh and
updates rural areas.
Therefore, you will see its numbers shooting up a bit,
but I think the
problems are now clear.
Long-term, I think this company and its
fundamentals from various sectors can
perform well. India's banking
sector, including children's small finance
bank scams, perform well in longitude.
Small finance banks'
first price for recovery is now very close to its current price.
If there is a slight decline of
two to three percent, then a festival of nine and a half to Rs
1000 can be a good start.
This is an important meeting for small finance
banks, but if you want to wait a little more,
if you feel that there are very few small or
mid-cap companies, and if there is a decline, there will be
some sensitivity in the
financial stocks in the lending business, then you
can tweet on WhatsApp with your eyes,
there can be special and active ground at 60
and digit good companies. I
think you have seen the fundamentals, remittances,
corporate governance,
better companies than others and small finance
bank sector to invest problem. The
next company can be looked at, India's leading French
company, Jox Confectionery, even
in dairy products, there are many good brands.
That company can be looked at, Britannia Industries. For
many days, it has been consolidating. We are looking at
Prince George's Momentum. Again, some of our
long-term movie new releases have come
around a good support level,
so that the level of 3334 or 350 to 3450 can
make a good support. You
can locate Britannia Industries for
accommodation for long term. Next price, wait for it.
It can be done with
301 fundamentals from 3000 to 31. This is a very good
company with a very good market share in HT
Biscuits, Kesar in the confectionery sector,
Yatri's dairy products, and also a good
brand name in Cricket Captain Industries.
So, I think its market share and
pricing power in the market is
not going to go away anytime soon. Its net profit
margin source numbers are quite good.
Rovella Stand 1528. So, I think this is a good
service company for long term. Idris
Company or 10 glass fit senior long-term
interest in the preamble.
Next, we will talk about that date.
Asian Paints is the market leader in the pet sector in India. Asian Paints is the market leader in the pet sector in India. Many videos have been released in the description of this app just an
hour ago.
Ambedkar Mission Team also
talked about two print center companies in the sector, Asian Paints and Birthday Parade. Some detailed
modifications were done. So, you can check this video and
write some idea about
why I consider Action Point such a great
player in up and  Sister,
for Asian Paints admission, I think that the
price of 24 to 25 will be reduced and travel
conditions will be very expensive. It is a very expensive stock. Its
valuation is done by many experts.
But still, I think that a price of
24 to 25 can be a good
starting point for accommodation in
Asian Paints. Next, you can wait for the price
of Bigg Boss tests. If you
want to wait for a price, then you can
bet. I think no problem,
whichever of these is more comfortable for you, then you
can start depositing capital. This is a very
fundamentally strong company and the
penetration of the paint sector in India is also a long way to go
from the data. The inspector is still on the growth runway and is
still quite good. The
next company which we will talk about is also
backwater. Because of this, its results were quite good before degradation. It
is a very strong company for its appointment and it creates monopoly in many sectors
like shares, like in
fast food, in front for wealth. Mary knows
chocolate.  It has a good market presence in many sectors
and the fundamentals of this
company are quite strong. I think the
current price level is 16,000 to 16,000 rupees, that is
why transmission can be started in between this
and can be looked for long term
investment. If you want to wait for the next price, then you
can do it in the range of 15,000
to 15,000 rupees. The leading company which we will
talk about next is HDFC Bank. It is
India's best private sector bank
and India's best bank overall.
So the best friend of India is
HDFC Bank. Definitely the first price level is
14,15 rupees,
it is in the middle of this market, so you
can start it if you want. The
second price level which you
can wait for is 12,13, if there is
such a big fall in the finance sector stocks, then there is a
possibility of
how much fall it is in a strong and
complicated situation, but if there is a
fall then 12,13 alone, thank you.
Cement long-term relationships at a very attractive price level The next bank I
like is Kotak Mahindra. This back retail
from Oriental Bank's office is quite
sensitive back end user name to be
conservative so I think its current
price can be a bit low for a good entry The
price level of 1718 is good
fashionable is noble price tag It is also quite
expensive Lutab extra which is good
conservative immediately Welcome hour They have very
expert valuations and Kotak
Mahindra Bank is no exception HDFC
Bank reaction is good and Kotak
Mahindra Bank This even more Halliburton
HDFC has intense past so still the first
offer missed like 1718 We can
wait for the second decision It is a little
lower It could be 14 to 15 and a half
If it surprises then definitely can make for a
good long term investment Back next
companies title In June business
growth in organized sector in India
Strong
pimp Its Tanish's sister  So many people trust
its property, a
well run company belongs to the Tata Group, so the
cash deposit asset is behind Titan
and I think that the jewellery business
organization has won its last
match award for the best players in 150 in this
world, which has the business of Ayurveda,
business of watches, in fact, it is a business, so it
also works in many decisions,
but to earn more than 80 percent profit
in the war, so let's get into the details and
type on all the businesses, so take a minute,
I think that the first price of the love sector is 14 in the
year 2014, which is its current price, if we take
it a little below, if there is a little more decline in
it, 3-4-5 percent, then it
definitely can make for a good investment
for long term examination, it can be done well, the
second reserve on that premises, if you
want to wait, you can do it, that is, a
turnover of 12.5 to 13, emerge a good
price payment at that time, ling tight, the next
company in such a sector, the
biggest player in India, Voltas, we have
talked about in many videos before Whirlpool India.  And it is
in the mid segment and
in other sets like refrigerators, ACs, washing
machines etc. Whirlpool
is a multinational company that manufactures everything but if we
talk about Voltas, it is also focused on exclusive ACs and could
not survive and the penetration of such businesses, such statements, is
very rare in India.
Welcome to our developing countries and
computer developed countries, so there is a lot of
penetration in the comments, so I think the growth
runway is good, such a company, in this, among the white
gold cement companies, Voltas can definitely be
seen as a long-term candidate.
I think that it may have suffered
losses due to the first price drop, due to which
it will fall a little around the earth
and if there is a decline in it, then
definitely 12 months ago it was in this price range.
We had sent notification for examination to some tech media people
who are currently associated with us on the Indian Telegraph channel,
many of them might have done it for only
1 minute and now it is
seeing some appreciation in the campus as well, so
whenever such strong staff, good support
levels  If we talk about item independence
then I will notify you on the Telegram channel
and according to my judgment
on my personal judgment my in waiting
for
Roopchand mentally can take a call that
if the cost of your investment is
profitable if these fit in routine work
then definitely canteen thing and
other preserve which can be updated
that is 860 thankfully that can also give very attractive
price will keep updating
how much you want after March
stay in stock one way moment endil about
salary so after fabric some consolidation
is visible in the stock for the first time and you
can take advantage of this consolidation keeping
staff in and watches and clippings support
levels in the ugly company in the life insurance
sector dynasty splash in India
private life insurance sector if we
talk then I like it the most
which is worthy and different from this its name
comparative analysis and
tie-up complaint for fundamental rights so I will
discuss in this video that such light
according to me  Why is HDFC Life most preferred in the f5 press?
But till now I
can tell you that its product range is so good,
financial year is good, it is a well-known
company, it belongs to such a group, so it has a
reputation in the market, people trust it because of its
fundamental attributes and quality, due to which
I especially like this website.
If life insurance enters, I
think that for a height minute, I can
say from the first point 6261 file of 675 and a half, the
second press level, if you want to weight it, then it can be
5 and a half level,
although the health of life insurance does
not fall much, if there is a
decline in the stocks of the financial sector, then
life insurance does
not fall without national insurance
because these are Chinese plate table players,
their Ganesh consistency keeps increasing,
but if you should weight that fashion, then it is
5 and a half to three-quarters inch, then it can be 5575
weight inside. You can talk amazing
platform next companies, multinational
pharmaceutical companies, embassy companies of
class 20 companies of  India Society of
India is the Indian subsidiary of Signature Pharma. It
can bring the first proposal to comment on it. 7575 has done fundamentally very well.
Its profit
growth, net merchants and press
performance over the past year, if you look at the performance of
cracked heels, this company has performed very well.
Secondly, if you
want to wait for it, it has been around 7070 for a long time. The
stress level answer site question and
consolidation is going on. Now you will see that
your airplane is also around 20 levels.
So right now, you can get the top 10 high not run on
petrol at a good valuation
and you are in a good consolidation phase
for democracy.
I think that
if this stock fits into your universe of films, then
10,000 good times to start
looking at the end of India. Next
committee meet, multinational pharmaceutical
company, this USPS does and the group  She belongs to
her Indian father-in-law and
is talking about Airport India
and you can see that it has been consolidating well for many days.
Right now
you are seeing it oscillating around Twenty20. There is not
much movement
in it. Time correction has been going on for a long time
and Indian, but I
think it is a company with strong fundamentals.
Many former secretaries have
monopoly in it or a very high market
share of more than fifty percent. That is a
very good price in power. Good fundamentals.
Saturday at free companies, written
letters are very good. The governor of multinational companies,
BSES is also very good. So
definitely share positive to inform about
India. I think if you provide research services
and if the performance is good and there is reasonable growth as compared
to the profit numbers, then
definitely the top 10
Naagin stars are moving in the opposite
direction. I think that it is expected to be
moving around the moving average of Tubeless. It has been
giving you opportunities for a long time to
apply, so different you can locate.  The
best company for long term investment,
first you should check and research
what this company does, in which pharma sector it is, what does
it manufacture, what is its market share, what is its
price in power, what is its net profit
margin, after checking all these things
if this company fits your needs in testing, then
definitely 10,000, good price,
loves and accommodation in which good support
levels for admission for long term, if you
want to compare it with the next price then you can do that,
it is 13,000 to 14000, if special is
reached then definitely chemical events for
dates problem, next compare
to
Kwid and only two less, meaning of three, four
wheeler makes commercial vehicles, Title Motors
in collaboration with small and small two
wheelers, if we talk about Royal Enfield, the
company which created the brand equal to create the grand vote, its
soul is Royal Enfield, there are many toys
in the bill, it has many other models than
350 cc  250 C and observe category,
Eicher Motors is a very good company creating a monopoly, friend note, I think Eicher Motors to admit,
again the same price lemon
juice, you can see that
it has been consolidating in the same state for the last four-five months,
so you can wait for the price of 24 and 25, come and
meet there, which
can be started, then in the middle of this price range, its
current price is in the middle of this price range,
so definitely you can consider
looking at Eicher Motors and long-term
investments, the next price which you
can wait for if you want to, is 21 and 22, so
please take it, friend, it is a good
price, just stop meeting Eicher Motors, the
next companies are giant monopoly creating
companies in the chemical sector in India, but if we
talk about the unit there, then if we talk about Sunrisers, then
Pidilite Industries is one of the
strongest players in the chemical business in the
contest in India,
it does not fall much.  There is a very
expensive elevation of the staff in the stock
but there
is so much monopoly in the market because of the weak residents and
time that if you talk about Doctor Fixit in the house then
except for Fevicol etc., you don't even hear the carpenter name anything,
meaning gum means
Fevicol, like people
call detergent as 'Tite' for WhatsApp, people call detergent as '
Surf Excel', washing soap as '
Korian', drama as 'Aashirwad',
similarly people call hot sentence as 'Fevicol',
whereas if there is no physical then
it is called Fevicol, so it gives you an
indication of what kind of
brand name has been created in the market,
still there is a college monopoly in the
weight reservations and similarly
in the waterproofing business the professor has made his friend, so roughly speaking we
can say that
deleted messages on various from players
in the telecom sector in India, I think
that its
current price is only 18 and a half from enemies, today
it falls a little
in the process, so I think  That a special
family could have been started, in this too there have been
celebrations for many days, let's say there has
n't been much decline, but
consolidation, let's say there haven't been many appointments, so
definitely this can be assured that enough to start looking at
Midnight Industries in the next process, if you
want to wait for it, you can do that for all
15716 there and in a little aggressive palace, the
list can be started in this match, the
next company is in the footwear segment,
along with Reliance and Tata, the company which creates details market, noise and branded, I like another company which is 400, I
like sound low fees, Bata India
team had already
updated its watch list of the best to sentiments and in
its discussion in the first few weeks, there was a
little movement of demos in it, Bata
Ghee, in this I have replaced it and
inputted you relax here
because through some consolidation in this, you will
see that you can also maintain your price level,
this festival in January, you know, it is still very
high, but it is consolidating on this channel, there is
not much decline  But there is
not much anger either. Did not
stop the
benefit fundamentals. So, therefore, I
think that the first price level
between 860 and 775 is a candidate for long-term relationships
and the second one, if you want to wait,
could be between 725 and 775. With its spices and
connections, it is even more attractive for
long-term investment. The next price level
in India in Gold Finance was running away from the problem market
and
Muthoot Finance, a company that has created a very good brand reputation, this
can be seen in the final company. It
works in Gold and works very well only
in exploited loans. I think
Mannapuram Finance is a good company right now.
Muthoot Finance because Mannapuram
Finance has an embassy, ​​but along with Gold, it is also
in many other segments and
in all those segments, Mannapuram Finance's
operations are not that good. At the same time, I
like these more. This exclusive
NVC company is consumer finance, but
Mannapuram Finance is in the sector.  55 is added to it. If we come to
consumer finance, then
for consumer finance,
I like market gold
more and for gold finance,
I like motor finance more.
Half of the time, because the popularity of gold has been
consolidating for a long time, there is a lot of download
pressure, so gold is
related to a lot of money.  That's Muthoot
Finance's promise, because their
gold
deposits activate with gold money. So,
consolidation has definitely been going on for a long time.
You'll see that the July decisions are just now, and
on the July festival of record, you should have seen
mutual funds a week ago. So, it can definitely be a
good practice to locate long-term investments
in annual functions. The first festival will cost you
1150 rupees, but
if you want to wait for it, if the
horse's identity is that much, then
definitely check your background. Muthoot
Finance, but the board's money. I think
that the place where time should invest in gold,
and I think Muthoot Finance is a candidate
from some play and gold investment, so
if this price level comes, the second one will be
9500 rupees, then it's a very good effort.
But don't have too much hope
that it will reach this level. Therefore, I
think that whichever of the two processes
suits you more and you feel more comfortable with,
start a million or
delay there.  Fundamentals
Shubhendu Fruit Company Point Investment in
Gold Finance Next Company India's another
big IT company TCS Infosys so they keep
talking about the problems in 2000
minute complete knowledge in IT sector but
this HCL Technologies not for B.Ed I
think this can very from clear
skin in front very from place its
quarters for kids were big evidence but all this was
duty because they had given
very good bonuses to their employees
introduction is certain revenue collection they had
set good revenue department stores all-time is remedy or
scheme is to their benefit so they gave
good bonuses to their employees due to
which profit margins keep declining a bit
but to
reduce the attrition for long term 10,000 good
look good management tips so that the
alteration rate will be controlled very low here
long term these can be forced in
its profitability 100 number so that's why
I think this seal testis  Definitely
one but in the IT sector Advocate 14 is
not even this principal session of HCL
Technologies. If you compare it in the IT sector with
Team
Infosys Siddharth which is a special
company, a well-valued company TCS Infosys to
I think there is some when
compared in it, so first press on it you
can see and its current price level is
around 9 in the middle of this price range, first press on it you can see it, then the first
press on it you can wash it, second press on it,
if you want to wait more and contact to
invest in it, then you
can wait for 800 to 500 WhatsApp messages,
boys in the world more attractive possible
for admission test championship, next
company is another favorite company of mine,
but in which I think that valuation can
also be dating and this investment can be
very blood relation for you,
very high investment project, you should
not invest in ITC, but I
think this can be one company that can be a
part of the  Government for your gift
means a very strong company. I
made a cigarette video on this that ward residents should
invest in Fortnite PC for long
term. Five reasons why it is man vs. So
this can definitely be a small part of your investment portfolio
because fundamentally it is a strong company. What
stretch companies, petrol companies, cigarette
balance stock companies, Adams are
creating good brands in this sector like
Sun Fees, Ashirwad flour, noodles.
You should know from ITC's Pran that it is trying to
create good brands in Film City.
You are trying to print from a good market.
ITC
Limited party has just come to its good
long-term support level. This is just a
moving average of many times. Friends, the
price of 205, we have entered this decision many times.
You can see that ITC has come to this
combination support level many times, that is, five-six times.
And there we often make
1 million in this price range.
If you see long-term potential in it, you
can arrest this video.
In this five press, one sack season, then 6 inches.
I have discussed personal
investment, but if you are a
little convinced there, if you feel
that yes, you have some results, like
in tempered glass etc., then definitely this
is the cost price of 200 to
205. If you want to wait for it, then you
can do that, this one is
185, 185. The next company
is a giant in the general insurance sector.
If we talk about the work of the biggest company in the private sector in the
general insurance sector, then there are
many good companies,
Weldon companies, companies with good fundamentals
and operate in good sectors,
general insurance, life insurance,
Celsius, etc. The period of the sector is very low
penetration in India, I see a long-term
earnings growth runway
in companies like ICICI Lombard. If you
want to invest in this company
for the long term, then the
first price is 13 and a half to 6 and a half, which you can watch up. The
second price level, which you can
wait if you want. From India, from 13 clothes,
clear fundamentals.  Values ​​from the company
operate in a good sector, penetration is very
low in India, when good crouch length
way ahead of impact, next companies
in the housing finance sector, India's leading
company with market share, the company with the largest
delegation and the best brand image,
Housing Development Finance
Corporation, HDFC Limited, sister mother
companies, I have such group companies like this
Pimp CR, HDFC Life, such like, the
fun company of all these, paint company, HDFC Limited, let's
talk about the company which is Khan Singh
Finance Company, for this topic, first price for 8 minutes, which is
around 2425, which is a record festival, definitely
built for long term investment
and spices, second question which if you
want to wait, now you can see
its moving average, it is around 237 125,
so 22
can take the fastest proposal and other problems, where if you
want to look at any company for admission, then
press inside their made, next company is HDFC Bank, another
company HDFC Assessment of this
remedy for  The dealers have declared their ID, which
Om has also said that Bigg Boss stock market has seen a
slight decline in the market
due to which this company has some management of its own
but I think that
for the long term I have a very well-thought-out company,
its distribution network is very good,
like banks help in its distribution,
many cards are difficult,
this is a good
to-do list for the long term, start
this, from 2800, Toubro can
press another button, if you want to wait for it, you
can do it, leaving 2425 and a half, the next company is
Adidas company for black,
Maruti Suzuki has
more than fifty percent market share in the passenger vehicle segment, although it has
used a little market,
Tata Motors has a good
aggressive strategy in electricals, due to which it has played a
little game with the market, so development
work is in progress, that I want to keep
track of your friend, if
you look at the long term investment potential
in it, then the current price is between 65 to 67, only that is why it has been
between inches and for many months.  The
shoulder is unstable, you can see the stop, even now
you will have to take Havells on the first half of August-September
and gas is at the level of 20 every
moment, so definitely you can consider this
company, but you need to do a little research,
Maruti Suzuki is very powerful in the Chinese sector, even if there is no
current, at this time the light is
very high in the baby segment,
less than electrical, and it is
losing a little from the market, these favored
players like Tata Motors, Hyundai, etc. to
tech
companies, after taking into account the ₹50 update,
if you think that there is
long-term potential, this company has just sold in the
last ₹500, it can be quite possible, a
good discount from its all-time high level,
you have other prices
which you can wait if you want, you can
wait comfortably, if you talk about the next
company, quality player in the electrical sector in India,
if you talk about difficult cable infection drops products, then the
name of Havells definitely comes up there,
you must have heard the name of this company,
its products are very good, there is a good
market.  There is concentration in the market, it is
much better than the biggest electrical
company, if you search in India, the
name of Half Inch is, it is the company with the biggest market
complex, so I think that to
update the waste, you
can see that after March there was a lot of
staying, for the first time there was consolidation
in this company, if you show in stop then you can
wait for almost all the 900 to 1000,
its family can be started there,
its current prices will be somewhere between Spice Jet,
press here, in the middle of this price range, it is
definitely attempted to long term
investment,
if you want to update, you
can see that the data movie is there
at 811, so I think that this holiday was to go to 298,
price traveled and looked for long
term investment, you can do
harvest management in minor,
from this long-term potential,
long-term goals scored in health,
patients of love depression, two-three in the last company
Indraprastha Gas Distribution Company
I especially like pots. This is
true of Gujarat. I like
Petrol Tank Limited, Metropolitan Joint Secretary of the Cardamom Yagnik investigation, as well as
Indraprastha Gas.
It
operates in some serious areas of Delhi NCR, Haryana, etc. Aunty,
its focus is on those locations. Naman has a
very strong company update free
companies. Many limited companies in different
areas that operate in. I think that for
8 minutes of IPL, 475 to 500 sale
candidate starting price level
president, acted as president, many times
support in this, this can be a good
president for long-term investments
and ideal. But if you want to wait a little,
if you think that the market
sentiment is a bit bad, there may be consolidation in the market, there may be a
slight correction, then you can
wait for a personal of 450 from the dreams of IPL.
There you can be started very Agrasen Chowk in maintenance
and Naman Telecom
Limited company, Gasprom companies and seeds, that is,
city gas distribution.
My favorite companies are those that can be good investments
for the long term. I think they can be a very good
investment. Gas supply
penetration isn't very high in India yet,
and due to environmental clearances,
pollution can be a factor. This is why
long-term goals can also be affected. Indore
City Gas Distribution Companies are under investigation only
for contemplation. City Gas
Distribution is a company that I hope,
friends, that the many companies we
discussed here, discussed their prices,
discussed their business, and you will
benefit from it. All these discussions can save your
soul and support for long-term
investment. This is my hope and belief. All these
will be helpful for you all throughout your
long-term investment thought process. So,
friends, today's video cassette, which is
Knowledge Power Screen, is a channel that aims to
bring the right knowledge to you.
In the upcoming videos, we will discuss many interesting
topics, and I will bring to you
Use Colloids and  The topic will be city, similarly
we will keep discussing weekly market updates and our
views and the situation left till now,
so this is definitely a subscribe to
Ajmer Poushtik Father, if you liked your last video
content then like the video,
if you feel that it
can help someone then share it with your friends and
family members and
subscribe to the channel, we will meet in our next
video with discussion of more topics, till then we are on
take care and new song